Exercise 6-13, Speed Reading. We've already practiced strong intonation, so
now we'll just pick up the speed. First, I'm going to read our familiar paragraph
as fast as I can. Subsequently, you'll practice on your own, and then we'll go
over it together, sentence by sentence, to let you practice reading very fast, right
after me. By then, you'll have more or less mastered the idea, so record yourself
reading really fast and with very strong intonation. Listen back to see if you
sound more fluent. Listen as I read. Hello, my name is Anne. I'm taking
American accent training. There's a lot to learn, but I hope to make it as enjoyable
as possible. I should pick up on the American intonation pattern pretty easily,
although the only way to get it is to practice all the time. I use the up and
down or peaks and valleys intonation more than I used to. I've been paying attention
to pitch, too. It's like walking down a staircase. I've been talking to a lot of
Americans lately, and they tell me that I'm easier to understand. Anyway, I could
go on and on, but the important thing is to listen well and sound good. Well, what
do you think? Do I? Pause the CD and practice speed reading on your own five
times. Repeat each sentence after me. Hello, my name is Anne. I'm taking
American accent training. There's a lot to learn, but I hope to make it as enjoyable
as possible. I should pick up on the American intonation pattern pretty easily,
although the only way to get it is to practice all the time. I use the up and
down or peaks and valleys intonation more than I used to. I've been paying attention
to pitch, too. It's like walking down a staircase. I've been talking to a lot of
Americans lately, and they tell me that I'm easier to understand. Anyway, I could
go on and on, but the important thing is to listen well and sound good. Well, what do
you think? Do I? Practice speed reading on your own five times. Repeat each sentence
after me. Record yourself speed reading with strong intonation.